ejuicevapor.com 2018-01-27

# Privacy Policy

**Email Information:**

Please do not provide sensitive personal information to us by e-mail. Instead, use our web forms, which employ SSL technology (see “How do we protect you and your information”). However, if you choose to correspond with us via email, we will retain the content of your email message together with your email address and our responses. We use administrative, technical and physical security measures to protect our computing infrastructure and your personal information from unauthorized use, access, modification or disclosure.

 **How do we protect visitor information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

 **Website (s) linked to**   **EJuiceVapor.com**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our website.

 **Privacy for Children:**

Children under the legal age of tobacco are not allowed to use our website and/or products. If you are under the legal tobacco age, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission from your parents or legal guardians.

 **Contact Us:**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, our website EJuiceVapor.com, or your order with us, please contact us.

 **Notice:**

EJuiceVapor.com reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time by direct electronic notification to you or by posting the amended terms on this page. All amended terms shall automatically be effective for new users or new purchases immediately on posting and, in all other cases, 30 days after they are initially posted and dated, unless otherwise specified in a notice to you.

Questions? Visit Our [Contact Us](https://www.ejuicevapor.com/pages/contact-us "Contact Us") Page!
